http://www.motoringsouthwest.org.au/index.php/contact/privacy

HomeEvent CalendarEvent DocumentsGalleryPast Event InvitationsPhotosVideoServicesSponsorsContactInfo LinksPrivacy Policy
Remember Me
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
Motoring Southwest Privacy Policy
1. Privacy Statement  Personal information collected by Motoring SouthWest is for the primary purpose of providing a better service to our customers. It will not be released for any form of commercial gain and will be maintained in a secure location as per the requirements of the Privacy Act 1998   2. Who Is Motoring SouthWest?  Motoring SouthWest is a democratically formed body made up of a Board of Directors for the purpose of promoting Motorsport at The Collie Motorplex, Powerhouse Rd, Collie, Western Australia
3. Collecting Your Personal Information  Motoring SouthWest understands that users may have concerns about their privacy and the confidentiality and security of information that Motoring SouthWest may obtain about them. Motoring SouthWest policy is to protect members’ privacy and personal information that it may collect from time to time. Motoring SouthWest has undertaken to comply with the requirements of the Privacy Act, 1988 and the National Privacy Principles included in the Privacy Act (Private Sector) Amendment Act 2000. Personal information is collected by Motoring SouthWest for the primary purpose of membership requirements / competition purposes / volunteer management. Motoring SouthWest may collect details such as your name, address, telephone and facsimile numbers, email addresses, gender, age, marital status, etc.  A hard copy file containing the member’s application and entry details are retained in a secure location in accordance with the act and for a further seven years in accordance with current Federal and State legislation governing document retention, before being destroyed.
4. What If You Do Not Provide The Personal Information We Require?
Failure to provide the information sought by Motoring SouthWest for the purposes detailed may not enable the organisation to use the products process or any specific service requested. i.e. Motoring SouthWest may not be able to include you in an event you may have entered or assign benefits to you as a user.
5. How Does Motoring SouthWest Secure Your Personal Information?  To prevent any unauthorised access to your information, Motoring SouthWest has installed computer and network security, including encryption and password protection processes.   Only staff authorised by the Chief Executive Officer have access to the data file information.  Hard copies of any information are stored in locked offices and equivalent off site secured storage areas.
6. To Whom Do We Disclose Your Personal Information?  A member’s personal information will only be used or disclosed by Motoring SouthWest as allowed by the Privacy Act 1988 and the National Privacy Principles included in the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act, 2000. Further, to conduct Motoring SouthWest operations, Motoring SouthWest occasionally engages independent operators and parties. Accordingly, some this information may be used or disclosed in part by Motoring SouthWest to:
Enable mail contractors to deliver documents and communications to members;
Officers of a government law enforcement agency in connection with the lawful performance of their duty;
A debt collection agency for financial default purposes;
Send direct mail to members with news of special offers or the availability of new products or services;
External advisors, including the associations representative body for the purposes of outsourcing the processing and servicing of member cheque's and the processing of user credit card payments
7. Withdrawing Your Consent  If you do not consent to any of the disclosures above  then you can write and advise Motoring SouthWest at its office address or contact Motoring SouthWest by telephone on 9734 7477. Motoring SouthWest will then ensure that your personal information is not used for this purpose. This exemption cannot apply where Motoring SouthWest is required by law to provide such disclosure.  If you do not object to the uses or disclosures as stated above, Motoring SouthWest will accept this as having received your express consent.
8. What If You Wish To Access Your Personal Information?  Users may, upon written request, access the personal information Motoring SouthWest has obtained from membership application forms and the related product or service forms that it currently holds. To the extent possible, Motoring SouthWest will let you access your personal information. However, there are times where the organisation is not in position to do so (e.g. where it would be unlawful to do so). If Motoring SouthWest denies you access to this information, Motoring SouthWest will notify you of this refusal and the basis for it. To cover administration costs of providing access to your personal information a charge may be applied. If so you will be notified of the cost prior to the information being made available.  To arrange access, please ask for details at the Motoring SouthWest head office on 9734 7477
9. What if you wish to change some of the personal information held?  Motoring SouthWest endeavours to ensure that personal information held is accurate, complete and up-to-date.  Where you believe that personal information held by Motoring SouthWest is not accurate, complete or up-to-date, then advise Motoring SouthWest and every effort will be made to correct the information.
10. What if you wish to lodge a complaint?All complaints associated with privacy matters must be in writing and directed to the manager of Motoring SouthWest. In the first instance, Motoring SouthWest can be contacted at its office on 9734 7477. Your call will initially be directed to the officer appointed by us to deal with your enquiry or complaint.
This Privacy Policy has been endorsed by the Committee of Motoring SouthWest
FOR FURTHER INFORMATION PLEASE MAKE CONTACT WITH...
Manager:   Anna Farrell
Mobile:      0428 826 613
Email:       This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Address:    Lot 643 Powerhouse Road Collie WA 6225
Postal:       PO Box 866 Collie WA 6225
FIND US ON FACEBOOK
Copyright © 2020 Collie Motoplex. All Rights Reserved.
Joomla! is Free Software released under the GNU General Public License.
Website Re-Created by Mike Farrell
